mylaps.com 2008-06-12

# Privacy - AMB Identification and Timing

**AMB Privacy Policy for the Internet**  
AMB believes strongly in protecting the privacy of the personally identifiable information you share with us, and respecting the permission you give us to use that information. (Personally identifiable information is information that can identify you by, for example, your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address.) We also believe it is important to disclose how we will use your information, and to give you choices about how it will be used. 

**Why should you share information with AMB i.t.?**  
Sharing your personally identifiable information enables us to offer you a number of benefits. This will make it easier and more convenient for you to: 

1\. Buy AMB products online  
2\. Register your purchase so you can receive all the benefits to which your purchase entitles you  
3\. Request information specific to your interests  
4\. Receive personalized messages and special offers that are relevant to your interests  
5\. Save time by storing your preferences 

It will also allow us to conduct market research to help us develop better products, to provide more responsive customer service and to improve our web sites. You may choose to share your information with us by completing an online registration form to enter a contest, register a purchase, participate in a promotion, subscribe to a newsletter or communicate with a customer care representative. Registration of your personal information always involves filling in a form. 

**Your choices**  
We want to know you better so we can serve you better. But the choice of whether you want this kind of service is up to you. We do not require visitors to AMB web sites to share personally identifiable information. 

We will only collect, use or share your personally identifiable information if you give us explicit permission to do so. By completing any online registration form (and checking/ticking the opt-in box where required by law), you are giving us permission to use and share your information under the rules set out below. If you provide us with personally identifiable information, you will have reasonable access to that information so you can change it, delete it or withdraw your permission for us to use or share it. You may do this by accessing your online profile, or by e-mailing or writing to us to request a copy of your profile at the contact address listed below. 

Because AMB sells thousands of products in 80 countries, you may have previously provided us with personally identifiable information through the warranty registration, or in some other manner. Your decision not to register now will not cancel contacts that occur as a result of your previous interactions with AMB. Of course, you will always have the option to unsubscribe to any online contact from AMB by changing your personal profile information. 

**Sharing information**  
You should know that by registering you are giving AMB permission to transfer your personally identifiable information from your home country exclusively to AMB divisions who may communicate with you about products or special offers you may find useful. AMB will not share any personal financial information you provide (such as credit card information) with other companies. From time to time, this website may provide links to other websites. You should carefully review the privacy policies on those sites; they may differ from the AMB Privacy Policy. AMB will never provide or sell our customer information including, but not limited to, emails, names, addresses, phone numbers or other personally identifiable information. 

**Cookies**  
Some of our web sites will send a "cookie," a small summary file, to your computer. This allows us to recognize your computer the next time you visit, without bothering you with another request to register. If you do not wish to receive cookies please refer to your Internet Browser to learn how to block all cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. To learn more about cookies we encourage you to visit [Cookie Central](http://www.cookiecentral.com/). 

**Safeguarding the information you share with us**  
We recognize our responsibility to protect the information you entrust to us. AMB uses a variety of secure techniques to protect your information, including secure servers, and encryption of financial data. AMB web sites also may make chat rooms, forums, message boards and/or newsgroups available to you. Please remember that any personally identifiable information that you provide in these areas becomes public information, and you should exercise caution in deciding to disclose it. It is important to note that AMB will release personally identifiable information if compelled by law. 

**Special information for children and parents**  
While AMB’s web sites are generally not targeted to children under the age of thirteen, it is AMB’s policy to comply with the law when it requires that a parent's or guardian's permission is secured before knowingly collecting, using or disclosing personal information of children under the age of 13. We strongly recommend that parents take an active role in supervising the online activity of their children. For more information we recommend that you visit the following web sites: 

**Contacting us**  
If you would like to contact us for any reason regarding our privacy policy you may contact us at [support@amb-it.com](mailto:support@amb-it.com). If you have a problem with our use of your information, please let us know and we will make all reasonable efforts to correct it. 

There are a number of excellent sources of information about online privacy and related issues. They include:
